oshopping.com.ph 2019-06-27

# Privacy Policy

The privacy and security of personal data collected from you – our customers, suppliers and trade partners – are important to A CJ O Shopping, Corporation. The officers and employees of A CJ O Shopping adhere to the principles of the Data Privacy Act of 2012 (RA 10173) (the “Data Privacy Act”), its implementing rules and regulations and rules, regulations and the relevant issuances of the National Privacy Commission of the Philippines (“NPC”) and comply with the best data privacy practices sanctioned in its Implementing Rules and Regulations and the relevant issuances of the National Privacy Commission of the Philippines (“NPC”) .   
This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) governs the collection, sharing, recording, updating, modification, retrieval, use, retention and disposal of Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information gathered pursuant to rendering services to our customers. 

TYPES OF INFORMATION COVERED BY THIS POLICY

This Policy applies to Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information. 

“Personal Information” is defined by law as any information, whether recorded in a material form or not, from which the identity of an individual is apparent or can be reasonably and directly ascertained by the entity holding the information, or when put together with other information would directly and certainly identify an individual. 

“Sensitive Personal Information” is likewise referred to as personal information:

  * About an individual’s race, ethnic origin, marital status, age, color, and religious, philosophical or political affiliations;
  * About an individual’s health, education, genetic or sexual life, or to any proceeding for any offense committed or alleged to have been committed by such individual, the disposal of such proceedings, or the sentence of any court in such proceedings;
  * Issued by government agencies peculiar to an individual which includes, but is not limited to, social security numbers, previous or current health records, licenses or its denials, suspension or revocation, and tax returns; and
  * Specifically established by an executive order or an act of Congress to be kept classified.

Information that does not identify or pertain to an individual person, such as anonymous, aggregated, or corporate data, is not covered by this Policy. We may collect, use and disclose such information in order to evaluate and improve and respond to the needs of our service offerings; communicate to our affiliates, sponsors, advertiser, service contractor; or for other purposes related to the our offered services. 

SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This Policy covers all Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information gathered by rendering our services through off-site purchases. 

DATA PROCESSING AND PROCEDURE

A CJ O shall ensure at all times that only authorized personnel may gain access to information and any violation to its set procedure will be accompanied by corrective measures and remedies within A CJ O. A CJ O also reserves its right to use the available legal remedies to correct any breach of protocol and procedure. 

Such procedures shall also be regularly monitored, modified, and updated to ensure that the rights of the customers are respected, and that processing thereof is done fully in accordance with the Data Privacy Act, and other applicable laws and regulations.

COLLECTION OF PERSONAL DATA

In the ordinary course of business through off-site sign-ups, A CJ O Shopping may collect your personal data such as your name, address, contact details, gender, marital status, age religious affiliation, health, or education, and other sensitive personal information.

ACJO may install “cookies” to help you personalize your experience with the Website. A “cookie” is a HTTP file that is placed on your browser by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your device. Its primary purpose is to provide our users with convenience in their browsing experience. For example, when you personalize websites to suit your preferences, or register with Linked Sites or services, a cookie helps the Website remember your behavioral information. Kindly note that on subsequent visits, this information can be retrieved to provide you with a faster and more customized browsing experience based on your preferences. 

Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by the web page server of the Website that issued it. You can modify your browser settings to accept or decline cookies. Unless you have modified your settings to decline cookies, it will automatically be installed when you continue to use the Website.

USE OF PERSONAL DATA

In general, we use the personal data collected to facilitate your transaction, administer your account with us, and most specially, to be more efficient in providing you with our products and services.

Furthermore, A CJ O may use your Personal Information and Sensitive Information for the following legitimate business purposes:

  * management and administrative purposes, which may include, but shall not be limited to, processing the customers’ requests, refunds as well as other updates regarding the services rendered;
  * to undertake research and profiling activities, with the aim to better the services offered and to know the needs of the customers in terms of the services being offered; provide training to employees and third-party agents in services-related queries, technical knowledge and skill, and any other related purposes of maintenance of A CJ O’s services;
  * market research purposes and in order to aid in the continuous development of A CJ O’s services which may include, but shall not be limited to the following purposes: (a) to conduct market studies or customer satisfaction surveys; (b) to personalize the A CJ O’s products and services, and; (c) to determine which offered products and services which A CJ O has the best feedback; 
  * advertising and promotion purposes, which may include, but shall not be limited to, campaign-based registration, the use of collected information by our marketing team for promos, such as raffles, offers, incentives and other rewards if you are eligible for the same, provided that you have consented to be notified or informed of the such offers, incentives and other rewards;
  * account security purposes, which may include, but shall not be limited to, notifying you of any service and security issues, preventing and detecting identity fraud, privacy breach or other crimes under the laws of the Republic of the Philippines, conducting internal audits and checking security measures in place; 
  * for purposes of compliance with legal and regulatory and requirements, which may include, but shall not be limited to, complying with requirements under applicable laws, rules and regulations in the Republic of the Philippines, or disclosing information to law enforcement agencies or government officials, as may be required by the said applicable laws, rules and regulations; and
  * for other legitimate business purposes, which business purposes shall be communicated to the customer.

NON-DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA

A CJ O Shopping will not disclose your personal information without your consent or in any circumstance not authorized by law or any valid order of court or government agencies. 

A CJ O may share Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information with A CJ O-related Companies, ABS-CBN Corp and its subsidiaries, affiliates, related entities, partners and third party agents in order to provide and manage all the needs of the customers in the most efficient and responsive means.

In the event of a bankruptcy, or a merger, acquisition, joint venture or other business transaction, involving our Site and applications, Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information may be transferred as part of the assets of the company, but will remain subject to this Privacy Policy.

Additionally, Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information may be disclosed without prior notice when A CJ O has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to protect or defend the legal rights or property of A CJ O, other A CJ O-related Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); to protect the safety and security of other A CJ O users or members of the public; to protect the integrity of products and services; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process.

A CJ O may share Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information with A CJ O-related Companies, ABS-CBN Corp and its subsidiaries, affiliates, related entities, partners and third party agents which will be covered by appropriate Data Sharing Agreements required under the present law. 

SECURITY OF PERSONAL DATA

Safety of all Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information collected is a top priority for A CJ O. A CJ O Shopping applies strict security measures and modern technologies to make sure your personal data are kept confidential and secured with us. Our employees are trained to handle your personal data with utmost confidentiality and we have internal control in place to avoid security breach or violation. 

Furthermore, We have implemented policies and procedures in accordance with the Data Privacy Act, related laws and issuances to provide an appropriate level of security for the Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information that we collect, record, update, modify, retrieve, use, store and dispose. We require that any other third parties to whom we disclose Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information governed by this Policy implement similar safeguards to protect Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information. 

In case of data breach involving Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information collected, stored, retained and used by A CJ O, individual notification to the persons affected will be sent electronically or in written form, in accordance with A CJ O’s breach management protocol as required by Data Privacy Act, related laws and issuances. 

If you have concerns about data breach involving information you have provided us, please send us an email at [dpo@acj.com.ph](mailto:dpo@acj.com.ph) or contact us at (+632) 808.0577. 

ACCESS AND DELETION

A CJ O gives you the option of editing, updating, modifying or removing your Personal Information and/or Sensitive Personal Information from A CJ O systems, which may include any and all information shared to A CJ O-related Companies, ABS-CBN Corp and its subsidiaries, affiliates, related entities, partners and third party agents. 

A CJ O retains Personal Information and Sensitive Personal information for a period of ten (10) years or as long as necessary to fulfill a legitimate business purpose. After this retention period, Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information in the A CJ O systems will be disposed of in accordance with provisions and procedures of applicable laws. 

If you need to access, correct, update, modify or delete any Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information you have provided to A CJ O, please send us an email at [dpo@acj.com.ph](mailto:dpo@acj.com.ph) or contact us at (+632) 808.0577. 

MODIFICATIONS TO THE POLICY

From time to time, A CJ O may update the Policy, as necessary and without prior notice, and will post the revised policy at <http://oshopping.com.ph/privacy-policy>. If we make material changes to the Policy that expand our rights to collect and/or use your Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information, we will notify you through the said website. 

This Privacy Policy is effective October 2017.

DATA PRIVACY RIGHTS

You may inquire or request for information regarding any matter relating to the processing of your personal data including the data privacy and security policies implemented by A CJ O Shopping to ensure the protection of your personal data. 

You may also request for an updating, rectification or amendment of your personal data or file complaint in case of any breach or violation of your data privacy 

You may send your inquiry or request to the following

Email : [dpo@acj.com.ph](mailto:dpo@acj.com.ph)

Letter : Office of the Data Privacy Officer  
7th Floor Avecshares Center, 1132 University Parkway North,  
Bonifacio Triangle, Bonifacio Global City, Taguig 1634 

Telephone : (+632) 808.0577
